RG 062:145, Town of Union
Connecticut State Library
Town of Union records
1796-1920
Connecticut State Library
Union (Conn.)
9 cubic feet
School and tax records fo the town of Union.
RG062_145
T000634
Historical Note
The town of Union was incorporated in October 1734.
Scope and Content
School and tax records fo the town of Union.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Schools -- Connecticut -- Union -- History -- Sources; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Union -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Union -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Union -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Union -- Registers
Places:
Union (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1796-1920
  - School society minutes, 1796-1857 (Box Box 1)
  - Second school district records, 1839-1901 (Box Box 1)
  - Second school district records, 1901-1909 (Box Box 1)
  - School vistors records, 1873-1898 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax abstracts
    Volumes for 1919 and 1920 are not boxed.
    - 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866-1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 2)
    - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 3)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box Box 4)
    - 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894 (Box Box 5)
    - 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 6)
    - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905 (Box Box 7)
    - 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 8)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918 (Box Box 9)
      On oversize shelving.
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume